Personal Data processed for the following purposes and using the following services:
------------------------------------------------------------------------------------

* Analytics

* Google Analytics and Google Analytics with anonymized IP  
    Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data
* Cloudflare Web Analytics  
    Personal Data: device information; language; Usage Data

* Contacting the User

* Contact form  
    Personal Data: email address; User ID
* Mailing list or newsletter  
    Personal Data: email address; Trackers; Usage Data

* Content performance and features testing (A/B testing)

* Google Optimize and Google Optimize 360  
    Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data

* Data transfer outside of the UK

* Data transfer abroad based on standard contractual clauses (UK), Data transfers according to a UK adequacy regulation and Other legal basis for Data transfer abroad (UK)  
    Personal Data: various types of Data

* Data transfer outside the EU

* Data transfer abroad based on standard contractual clauses, Data transfer to countries that guarantee European standards and Other legal basis for Data transfer abroad  
    Personal Data: various types of Data

* Device permissions for Personal Data access

* Device permissions for Personal Data access  
    Personal Data: Camera permission, without saving or recording; Microphone permission, without recording; Storage permission

* Displaying content from external platforms

* Google Fonts  
    Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data

* Handling payments

* Apple Pay, Stripe and PayPal  
    Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service
* Payments processed via the Apple App Store  
    Personal Data: purchase history

* Platform services and hosting

* Google Play Store  
    Personal Data: Usage Data

* Registration and authentication

* Auth0  
    Personal Data: email address; first name; last name; password; picture; Trackers; various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

* Remarketing and behavioral targeting

* Google Ads Remarketing  
    Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data

* SPAM protection

* Google reCAPTCHA  
    Personal Data: answers to questions; clicks; keypress events; motion sensor events; mouse movements; scroll position; touch events; Trackers; Usage Data

* Tag Management

* Google Tag Manager  
    Personal Data: Trackers; Usage Data

* Traffic optimization and distribution

* Cloudflare  
    Personal Data: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service

Information on opting out of interest-based advertising
-------------------------------------------------------

In addition to any opt-out feature provided by any of the services listed in this document, Users may follow the instructions provided by [YourOnlineChoices](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.youronlinechoices.com/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1684952970653987&usg=AOvVaw11ewu89LAWe1eMHRANmLr-) (EU), the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://thenai.org/about-online-advertising/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1684952970654274&usg=AOvVaw1dQKrYn3D4BuTcnXIsYEOA) (US) and the [Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://www.aboutads.info/consumers/&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1684952970654460&usg=AOvVaw2aYKiDVpXjlJz1QrLs8JXx) (US), [DAAC](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://youradchoices.ca/understanding-online-advertising&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1684952970654676&usg=AOvVaw3NUIvAj1LHHjlU9JVr8__Y)(Canada), [DDAI](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.ddai.info/optout&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1684952970654852&usg=AOvVaw18TNi2HBwZjWzHnGGUsc8-) (Japan) or other similar initiatives. Such initiatives allow Users to select their tracking preferences for most of the advertising tools. The Owner thus recommends that Users make use of these resources in addition to the information provided in this document.

The Digital Advertising Alliance offers an application called [AppChoices](https://www.google.com/url?q=https://youradchoices.com/appchoices&sa=D&source=editors&ust=1684952970655119&usg=AOvVaw3K3OIQ-dYqCvc77_m7ErW_) that helps Users to control interest-based advertising on mobile apps.

Users may also opt-out of certain advertising features through applicable device settings, such as the device advertising settings for mobile phones or ads settings in general.

Further information about the processing of Personal Data
---------------------------------------------------------

* Equal protection of User Data  
    activatevpn.com shares User Data only with third parties carefully selected to ensure that they provide the same or equal protection of User Data as stated in this privacy policy and requested by applicable data protection laws. Further information on data processing and privacy practices by third parties can be found in their respective privacy policies.
* Selling goods and services online  
    The Personal Data collected are used to provide the User with services or to sell goods, including payment and possible delivery.  
    The Personal Data collected to complete the payment may include the credit card, the bank account used for the transfer, or any other means of payment envisaged. The kind of Data collected by activatevpn.com depends on the payment system used.

Contact information
-------------------

* Owner and Data Controller  
    Activate Software LLC  
    16192 Coastal Highway  
    Lewes, DE, 19958  
    Owner contact: [activatevpn.com/contact](https://activatevpn.com/contact)
